

FRONT END DEVELOPER

#### Details

Shenzhen, China <u>8613148723062</u> kuangdan23062@gmail.com

#### Links

<u>Portfolio</u> <u>Github</u> <u>LinkedIn</u> Instagram

#### Skills

## Programming Languages

JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML&CSS, Sass, GraphQL

## **Libraries & Frameworks**

React, Vue, jQuery,
Next.js, Node.js, Express,
Koa, Tailwindcss, Styled
Components, Ant Design,
ElementUI

## **Tools & Platforms**

Webpack, Vite, Git

## Languages

Mandarin, English

## Education

Master Degree, International Relations, China Foreign Affairs University

## **Profile**

A frontend developer over 7 years with experiences in the industry of e-commerce and building in-house systems of a large chain supermarket. Conducted over 10 e-commerce related projects, and more than 5 admin dashboard systems, including pc and mobile oriented web applications. Proficient in an assortment of technologies, including JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React, Redux, Typescript, Node.js, Next.js, Axios, etc.

## **Employment History**

# Senior Frontend Developer, Yonghui Supermarket Corporation, Beijing OCTOBER 2018 - APRIL 2022

- Wrote modern, performant, maintainable code for in-house projects, including monitoring system, shop devices management system, marketing campaign planning system, server management system, etc
- Using different languages, frameworks, and libraries such as JavaScript, React, Redux, Ant Design, TypeScript, Styled Components, Node.js, Vue.js, Vuex. ElementUI. WebSocket
- Communicated with multi-disciplinary teams of engineers, product managers on a regular basis
- Provided effective troubleshooting and remediation for web applications

#### Frontend Developer, Sao Tianxia, Beijing

JUNE 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2018

- Planned, developed, tested and maintained web applications, mostly mobile first responsive web interfaces, including various QR-code based e-commerce user interfaces
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and systems requirements
- Worked with Vue.js, Vuex, CSS3, SASS, ElementUI, Webpack, Gulp to build web pages on different sizes of mobile phones
- Followed policies and procedures related to application methods and quality standards at all times
- Regular performed interviewing and hiring junior frontend engineer procedure

#### Frontend Developer, Zhu Baijia, Beijing

SEPTEMBER 2015 - JUNE 2016

- Built a web application for a hotel and homestay booking platform, including pc website, wap and hybrid pages
- Developed and maintained code primarily using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and iOuery
- Worked at an independent level, while also serving as an effective and enthusiastic collaborator

# **Personal Projects**

## **Chat Room**

Sep 2022

A real-time chat room using Express, JWT, Socket.io, React and Tailwindcss

## **Headless CMS Blog**

June 2022

A responsive blog website with featured and recent posts, categories. full markdown articles, author information, comments, etc. Using React, Next.js, GraphQl, Tailwindcss